有问题吗
Problem?
这是我吃过最难吃的脆皮水果派
This is the worst cobbler I've ever eaten.
味道就跟出自一个初级的补鞋匠之手一样
It tastes like it's made of actual ground-up shoemaker.
真好笑  "cobbler"一词两意都点到了
Amusing. A play on the two meanings of "cobbler."
伙计们  猜猜我在洛杉矶机场发现谁了
Hey   guys. Guess who I found at LAX?
我的妹妹普丽娅
My baby sister Priya.
抱歉  我反对
Excuse me   I object.
你提出的是一个猜谜游戏
You propose a guessing game
可是你一点猜的时间都不给我
yet you don't give me enough time to guess.
声明一下  我本来就打算说
For the record   I was going to say:
"你的妹妹普丽娅"
"Your sister Priya."
谢尔顿  你一点都没变  对吧
Oh   Sheldon. You haven't changed a bit   have you?
我为什么要变
Why would I change?
她的本意其实是
The hope has been that
你最终能变得正常一点
you'd eventually bend to public opinion.
普丽娅  什么风把你吹来洛杉矶
So   Priya   what brings you back to L.A.?
我本来要去多伦多  但我得在这滞留一天
I have a one-day layover on my way to Toronto.
企业并购
Corporate merger.
你们相信吗
Can you believe it?
小普丽娅是印度最大汽车公司
Little Priya's one of the lead attorneys
首席律师之一
for the biggest car company in India.
鉴于当时咱们见面  她已经从法学院毕业了
Given that when we met her   she was finishing law school
而且正打算去一家大的印度汽车公司实习
and planning an internship at a large Indian car company
这个结果其实相当合理
it's actually extremely plausible.
你怎么就这么惹人嫌呢
And your poll numbers just keep dropping.
虽然我很想跟大家一起聊聊
I want to catch up with all of you
但我得先去上个厕所
but first I really must visit the loo.
我也去  我给你指路吧
I'm going   too; I'll show you where it is.
好的  虽然这不用明讲
All right   this goes without saying
但是无论如何我还是重申一下
but I'm just going to say it anyway.
不许碰我妹妹
Hands off my sister.
我干嘛碰她  她浑身布满了飞机细菌
Why would I touch her? She's covered with airplane germs.
我当然不是跟你说  我是跟他说
I'm so not talking to you. I'm talking to him.
-喂  我都是有女朋友的人了  -拜托
- Hey. I've got a girlfriend now.  - Oh   please.
我的妹妹比你那女友辣多了
My sister's much hotter than your girlfriend
这点你心知肚明
and you know it.
她们俩都很辣行了吧
Let's just agree they're both hot.
但是伙计  你说的可是我妹妹
But dude   that's my sister you're talking about!
算了  不说这个话题
Okay   forget who's hotter.
普丽娅第一次来洛杉矶时  我和莱纳德
The first time Priya came to L.A.   Leonard and I made a pact
出于对我们友情以及对你的尊敬
out of respect to our friendship and to you
我们约定  谁也不能泡你妹妹
that neither of us would hit on her.
你们拉钩钩了吗
Did you pinky-swear?
当然
Yes.
那好吧
Okay   then.
补鞋匠的水果派  我到现在还忍不住发笑
Cobbler. I'm still laughing.
真高兴再次见到你 莱纳德
It's really nice to see you again   Leonard.
是啊  我也很高兴见到你
Yeah. It's good to see you   too.
你到了
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
哇哦  哇哦  哇哦
Whoa   whoa   whoa   whoa   whoa!
继续
Okay.
生活大爆炸
第四季第六集
你跟你的妹妹有什么特别计划吗
So you got any special plans with your sister?
没有  就是一起出去玩
Oh   not really. Just hang out.
我总是跟人说  如果你只能在
I always tell people   "If you have only one day
洛杉矶呆一天  火车一日游是最佳选择
in Los Angeles   make it a train day."
火车一日游
Train day?
乐趣始于在影城的卡尼餐厅吃早午饭
The fun starts with brunch at Carney's in Studio City
在改造过的铁路餐车里  有一个热狗站
a hotdog stand in a converted railroad dining car.
下一站  Travel Town
Next stop   Travel Town
一家户外的博物馆  专门展出1880年至1930年的
an outdoor museum featuring 43 railroad engines
铁路引擎  汽车  和其他轨道车辆
cars   and other rolling stock from the 1880s to the 1930s.
最后  我们在浮华与魅力并存的好莱坞下车
And   finally   we're off to the glitz and glamour of Hollywood
对  就在好莱坞的卡尼餐厅吃晚饭
for dinner at--that's right-- the Hollywood Carney's
那是另外一个改造过的铁路餐车热狗站
a hotdog stand in a different converted railroad dining car.
我们才不会玩这个
I don't think we're going to do that.
显然  你讨厌寻乐
Well   then apparently you hate fun.
普丽娅还没回来呢
Priya's not back yet?
这很正常
Well   I guess that's not unusual.
女人  男人  一个蹲着一个站着
Women   men   the whole sitting-standing deal.
咱们刚才聊到哪里了
So what are we talking about?
我和普丽娅的出游计划
Uh   my plans with Priya.
他拒绝火车一日游
He rejected Train Day.
你有说清楚那是两辆不同的火车车厢
Did you make it clear that it's two different train cars
改造成的热狗站吗
turned into hotdog stands?
十分清楚
Abundantly.
我想他就是讨厌寻乐
I guess he just hates fun.
我也是这么说的
That's what I said!
好了  你们有什么新闻
Okay   so... what's new with you guys?
我有女朋友了
I have a girlfriend now.
不错嘛
Hey   good for you!
嗯  我就想让大家都知道
Yeah   I just want to put it out there
以防我不经意
in case I inadvertently
朝你喷射出我的性引诱外激素
squirt any pheromones in your direction.
满意了吧
Happy?
普丽娅  你有什么安排吗
So   Priya   what are your plans while you're here?
我不知道  我只有一天时间
I don't know. I just have the one day.
你喜欢火车吗
Do you like trains?
不是特别喜欢
Not particularly.
那你在机场上等着登机就好了
You might as well just wait at the airport for your flight.
你在一片森林当中
"You are in a forest.
在西面  有一片流沙
"There is quicksand to the west
有一条通向东面的路
a path leads to the east."
去东面
Go east.
一道铁门挡住了你的路
"An iron gate blocks your way."
开门
Open gate.
上锁了
"It's locked."
这样啊
Hmm.
那算了
Well   so much for that.
很晚了  你怎么还不睡
It's getting pretty late. How come you're still up?
我刚在网上发现了一款游戏模拟器
I found an emulator online that lets you play classic text-based
可以玩上世纪80年代的经典文字游戏
computer games from the 1980s.
不错啊
That's pretty cool.
当然了  因为它用到了世界上最强大的图像处理器
Oh   yes. It runs on the world's most powerful graphics chip:
想象力
imagination.
你倒是真该好好发掘一下
You've really got to get out more.
向北走
Go north.
你不能走这条路
"You can't go that way."
向西走
Go west.
巨魔挡住了你的道路
"A troll blocks your passage."
好吧  系好你的安全带
Okay. Fasten your seatbelts.
剿灭巨魔
Kill troll.
用什么
"With what?"
用剑
With sword.
你没有剑
"You don't have the sword."
天呐  这种倒霉事真降临到我头上了
Good golly   it's as if it's actually happening to me.
拉杰总算上床睡了
Raj finally went to bed.
可谢尔顿还没睡
Sheldon's still up.
你跟我说过他九点会睡的
You said he goes to bed at 9:00.
他的确应该睡了  但他刚痴迷于一款电脑游戏...
Yeah   he does   but he got caught up in a computer game and...
用斧头击杀巨魔
Hit troll with axe!
服了  这真是个顽强的巨魔
My   this is one tough troll.
你没法摆脱他吗
Can't you get rid of him?
根据以往经验  不可能
If the past is any indication   no.
莱纳德  我陷进流沙里了
Leonard   I'm trapped in quicksand!
这斧头在拖我下去呢
The axe is dragging me down!
扔掉斧头
Drop axe!
扔掉斧头  英明
Drop axe   brilliant!
稍等一下
Give me a minute.
-谢尔顿  -等一下
- Sheldon. - Hold on.
我正在思考如何能拿到桶
Trying to figure out how to get the bucket
这样我就能扛着泥土越过那条龙了
so I can carry the mud past the dragon.
-谢尔顿  你还得早起工作呢  -我知道
- Sheldon   you need to work in the morning. - I know!
那还不赶紧睡觉
Well   then bed   mister!
再给我五分钟嘛
Five more minutes!
你确定吗
Really?
你打算冒着在热力波动学研讨会上打瞌睡的
You're going to risk getting sleepy in the middle of your
风险继续玩下去吗
thermodynamic fluctuations seminar?
你知道自己在公众面前打哈欠的后果吧
You know what happens when you yawn in public.
大家都会看着我形态奇异的小舌头
Everyone will see my oddly shaped uvula.
你也不想看到这个画面吧
You don't want that   do you?
不想
No.
但我们社会嘲笑奇异舌头的做法是可耻的
But it's a shame our society mocks the differently uvulated.
刚才谁敲门了
Who was at the door?
呃  楼管员
Uh   building manager.
他们要来修个管子
They have to fix a pipe
所以明天中午到下午两点会停水
so the water'll be off tomorrow from noon to 2:00.
这是让人无法接受的
That's unacceptable.
我们理应提前得到书面通知的
We're supposed to be given written notice.
没关系的  反正我们到时候也是在工作的
Well   no   it doesn't matter-- we'll be at work.
如果我不小心把番茄汤撒到衣服上怎么办
What if I spill tomato soup on my shirt
我必须回家来换
and have to come home to change
结果发现没有水来泡洗衣粉吗
only to find there's no water for an enzyme soak?
别忘了分叉的小舌头  谢尔顿
Bifurcated uvula   Sheldon!
那我明天吃鸡肉面吧  晚安
I'll have the chicken noodle. Good night!
我们一定得注意小声点
We're going to have to be very quiet.
我想到如何拿到桶了
I know how to get the bucket!
我可以反过来握斧头
I can turn the axe around
然后用斧头把钩到水桶
and use the handle to reach it.
让我试试
Let's see.
向北走
Go north.
你现在身处森林
"You are in a forest."
继续向北走
Go north.
你仍然身处森林
"You are in a forest."
再往北走呢
Go north.
你还是身处森林  天呐  我想我迷路了
"You are in a forest." Oh dear   I believe I'm lost.
我还是明天从头再玩吧
Well   I'll just have to get a fresh start tomorrow.
不不不  你刚才只不过方向搞错了而已
No   no   no! You just took a wrong turn.
你只要把图画出来就行了
You just need to map it out.
来吧  我来帮你
Come on   I'll help you.
你停在了小溪旁  然后向北走了三次对吧
So you stopped at the stream   and you turned north three times?
是的
Yes.
你说对了  你是迷路了  祝你好运
You're right. You're lost. Good luck.
莱纳德  醒醒
Leonard. Wake up.
抱歉
Huh? Wh-- Sorry.
抱歉什么啊
For what?
我也不知道  只要我跟女孩子同床共枕后
I don't know. When I'm in bed with a girl   it's just--
这就是我的条件反射应答
it's my go-to response.
已经六点了  我得在拉杰睡醒
It's 6:00. I have to get back to Raj's
发现我不见了之前  赶紧回去了
before he wakes up and realizes I'm gone.
哦  那好吧
Oh. Right. Sure.
我真希望你能在洛杉矶待久点
I wish you could stay in L.A. a while longer.
我也想啊
Mmm   me   too.
知道吗  我刚才一直在想
You know   I was thinking
印度其实也有这么多先进的实验设施了
there are some great research facilities in India.
你想说什么  莱纳德
Where are you going with this   Leonard?
我其实想说  反正我在这也没啥牵挂
Well   I'm just saying   you know   I don't have any real ties here
我也可以搬去新德里[印度城市]  我们可以一起  你懂得
so if I were to move to New Delhi   we could   you know--
出去玩玩
go out.
莱纳德  我们五年前不就谈过这个了吗
Leonard   didn't we have this conversation five years ago?
是这样的  但是...
Well   yes   but...
今非昔比了嘛
things have changed.
你也长大了  我也长大了
You know   you're older   I'm older--
看吧  再也没什么漫画英雄的床单了
Look   no more superhero bed sheets.
亲爱的
Sweetheart
我们在一起很愉快  并不意味着
just because we have fun when I come to town doesn't mean
我想要开展一段正式的感情生活
I want to have a serious relationship.
-不想吗  -不想
- It doesn't? - Mm-mm.
此外  我永远也不可能介绍个白种男孩给我的父母
And besides   I could never bring a white boy home to my parents.
他们宁愿要头牛
They'd have a cow.
这在印度可就很大件事了
Which is a much bigger deal in India.
我也没很纯的白人血统啦
I'm not that white.
我的高祖母有一半彻罗基[印第安族]血统
My great-great-grandmother was half Cherokee.
我知道虽然不是真正的印度血统  但也算印什么了啊
I know that's not the right kind of Indian   but it is something.
你真有趣
You're funny.
莱纳德
Leonard?
啥事
What?
我听到了女人的笑声
I heard a woman laughing.
哦  我刚才想试试自己能否笑得像个女人
Oh   uh   yeah. I was trying to see if I could laugh as a woman.
哦  那做的不错啊  很真实啊
Oh! Well   good job. Quite convincing.
我闻到了香水味
I smell perfume.
空气清洗剂的味道
Air freshener.
你这脸颊和脖子上是口红吗
And is that lipstick on your cheek and neck?
是疹子  很严重的疹子
Rash. That's a bad rash.
深表同情
My sympathies.
我很了解这种红色祸害  也就是皮炎
I'm no stranger to the crimson scourge that is dermatitis.
我在我的乳液和软膏系列里
Can I interest you in a topical steroid
帮你找一种管用的类固醇好吗
from my lotion and unguent collection?
好啊  好啊  这主意不错
Uh   yeah   yeah   that sounds great.
很好  我相信我可以找到
Very well. I'm sure I can find something
帮你止痒的东西
that will help you ditch that itch.
好了  他去洗手间了  我们走
Okay   he's in the bathroom. Let's go.
你喜欢软膏还是霜剂
Do you prefer ointment or cream?
霜剂
Cream.
要不要含麻醉添加剂的
With or without a numbing agent?
不要
Without.
真的吗  莱纳德
Really   Leonard?
有皮炎的时候可不能逞英雄
There are no heroes when it comes to dermatitis.
好吧  那就要
Fine. With.
处方药还是非处方的强效药
Prescription or non-prescription strength?
发挥你的判断力吧
Use your best judgment.
我有一支很不错的2009年的肛泰软膏
Well   I think I have a nice 2009 AnaMantle HC.
通常是针对严重发炎的痔疮的
It's usually indicated for acutely inflamed hemorrhoids
但是对非粘膜器官也管用
but it also goes nicely with non-mucosal body parts.
听起来不错
Sounds great.
明智的选择
Excellent choice.
好了  快点  快点  快点
Okay   hurry   hurry   hurry.
快走  快走  快走
Come on   come on   come on.
普丽娅
Priya?
早上好  谢尔顿
Good morning   Sheldon.
羞耻呀  莱纳德  羞耻
For shame   Leonard   for shame.
我居然还差点准备
And to think   I was ready to waste
把我最后一点好用的痔疮霜浪费在你身上
the last of my good hemorrhoid cream on you.
挺开心的啊
Making pretty good time   huh?
你真的想说这个吗  莱纳德
Is that really what you want to talk about   Leonard?
不是
No.
那你想说什么
What do you want to talk about?
拜托别跟任何人说
Please don't tell anyone
我跟拉杰的妹妹过夜了
I spent the night with Raj's sister.
说出来了
There it is.
要是有人问起来呢
What if someone asks?
没人会问我是不是跟拉杰的妹妹过夜了
No one's going to ask if I spent the night with Raj's sister.
或许吧  但是他们可能会问我别的
Perhaps   but they might ask me something else.
-比如呢  -比如说
- Like what?  - Like
莱纳德最近有没有做出背叛朋友的行为
"Has Leonard betrayed any of his friends recently?"
普丽娅和我都是成年人了
Priya and I are both adults.
我没有背叛拉杰
I didn't betray Raj.
你有  但是我指的是霍华德
In fact   you did   but I was referring to Howard.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
2005年4月12日
April 12   2005.
在图卢卡湖的鲍勃大头娃汉堡店里
Bob's Big Boy   Toluca Lake.
拉杰第一次把普丽娅介绍给我们
Raj had just introduced us to Priya for the first time.
她正在享受印度教禁止的美味食物
She was enjoying the sweet taste of Hindu rebellion
那就是鲍勃超级大头娃牛肉堡
in the form of a Bob's Super Big Boy hamburger.
为了维护你们的友谊
In order to preserve your friendship
你和霍华德发拉钩钩说
you and Howard made a pinky swear
你们俩人都不许追求她
that neither of you would attempt to woo her.
我点了一份奶酪牛肉片
I had a patty melt.
好吧  我背叛了霍华德
Okay   fine   I betrayed Howard.
-还有拉杰  -好的  还有拉杰
- And Raj.  - All right   and Raj.
还有我
And me.
你
You?
你违反了室友协议中
Violation of the Roommate Agreement's
有留宿客人要提前通知之一条款
overnight guest notification clause.
好吧  我是个令人讨厌的家伙
Okay   fine   I-I'm a horrible human being.
我就是帕萨迪纳的达斯·维达
I'm the Darth Vader of Pasadena.
你当达斯·维达还太矮了点
You're far too short to be Darth Vader.
你最多也就是叛徒伊渥克[星球大战]
At best you might be a turncoat Ewok.
我只是想说  普丽娅已经走了
My point is: Priya's gone and it would be much better
要是没人知道这件事就最好了
if no one else found out about us.
你是说你想让我帮你保密
You mean you want me to keep a secret?
是的
Yes.
你知道我是保守不了秘密的
You know I can't keep a secret.
你努力尝试的话就可以的
You can if you try.
就这样想
Think about it this way:
如果我是蝙蝠侠  你是艾尔福
um   if I were Batman and you were Alfred
你一定可以对我的身份保密  对吧
you'd keep that secret   right?
凭什么你是蝙蝠侠
Why do you get to be Batman?
因为蝙蝠侠才有身份的秘密呀
Because Batman has the secret.
艾尔福也有秘密的
Alfred has secrets   too.
-什么秘密  -艾尔福知道
- Like what?  - Alfred knows
芭芭拉·科尔顿是蝙蝠女
that Barbara Gordon is Batgirl.
而我刚刚就把这个秘密告诉了蝙蝠侠
Which I've now just told to Batman.
你看  我就是保守不了秘密
See   I cannot keep a secret.
挞哒
Ta-dah!
什么
What?
挞哒
Ta-dah.
这是
It's short for...
哒哒哒哒的缩减版
Da-da-da-da! ?
谢尔顿  我正忙着呢
Kind of busy here   Sheldon.
我知道  所以我才缩减了
I know   that's why I shortened it.
你想干吗
What do you want?
我是来给你提供昨晚的不在场证明的
I came to go over your alibi for last night.
什么不在场证明
What alibi?
你让我替你撒谎  而你也知道
You've asked me to lie on your behalf   and as you know
我很讨厌没有提前准备的谎言
I am deeply uncomfortable with impromptu dishonesty
所以我就给你准备了不在场的铁证
so I've provided you with an ironclad alibi.
你昨晚不可能跟普丽娅过夜
You couldn't have spent last night with Priya
因为你跟另一个女人在一起
because you were with another woman.
我一定会后悔的
Oh   I'm so sure I'm gonna regret this
但我还是要问  我跟谁在一起
but who was I with?
风趣但作风随便的麦琪·麦凯瑞小姐
The fun-loving and morally loose Miss Maggie McGarry.
天啊
Oh   God.
你们是在帕萨迪纳最有名的
You met her at Pasadena's most popular
爱尔兰酒吧  幸运鲍德温酒吧认识的
Irish watering hole   Lucky Baldwin's
麦琪是那里的吧台服务员
where Maggie spends her nights tending bar
她一头卷发  心怀梦想
with a head full of curls and a heart full of dreams.
莱纳德  想要苟合的话就打给我
"Leonard   call me if you are interested in coitus.
麦琪·麦凯瑞敬上
Sincerely   Maggie McGarry."
如果真的有人
And if anyone were
打这个号码查证的话  他们会听到
to actually call that number   they will hear this.
祝你有个美好的早晨
Top of the morning to you.
这里是麦琪·麦凯瑞家
You've reached Maggie McGarry.
在轻盈的哔声后请留言
Leave a message after the wee little beep.
很真吧
It's pretty convincing   huh?
那都不是真人发声
That wasn't even a real person.
最后还有
And here is the clincher:
一撮麦琪的红棕色头发
a lock of Maggie's flaming auburn hair.
你这是从哪弄来的
Where'd you get that?
从灵长类实验室的红毛猩猩身上剪的
From an orangutan in the primate lab.
红毛猩猩
An orangutan?
又没人会去验DNA  莱纳德
Well   no one's going to run a DNA test on it   Leonard.
说真的  你想得太多了
Honestly   you overthink everything.
谢尔顿  我不需要不在场证明
Sheldon   I don't need an alibi.
只要你不乱说话
Nobody's going to ask about last night
没人会问昨晚的事的
as long as you just zip your lip.
谢了
Thank you.
别担心  不会有事的
Now   don't worry   everything is going to be fine.
莱纳德  你能不能告诉霍华德
Hey   Leonard   will you please tell Howard
我妹妹从没喜欢过他
my sister has never been attracted to him?
得了  拉杰
Come on   Raj
我怎么知道你妹妹
how am I supposed to know
现在喜欢谁  以前喜欢过谁
who she is attracted to or was attracted to
将来又会喜欢上谁啊
or who she might be attracted to in the future?
我对这个话题
And I have nothing to contribute
毫无建设性意见
to this conversation.
因为我也完全不知道
Because I   too   know absolutely nothing
普丽娅对男性伴侣的偏好
about Priya's preferences in male companionship.
所以  我会再次闭上嘴
And with that   I will re-zip my lip.
对了  你们觉得昨晚
Hey   so what did you guys think
卡布里卡的最新一集怎么样
of the new episode of Caprica last night?
我没看
I didn't see it.
啥  没看
Didn't see it?
那你在干什么
What were you doing?
我出去了
Uh   I was out.
啥  昨天可是卡布里卡之夜
What   on Caprica night?
是啊  我出去喝了一杯
Yeah   I   uh   went for a drink.
真的假的  就你
Really   you?
你去哪儿了
Where   w-where'd you go?
去了...
To   uh...
幸运鲍德温酒吧
Lucky Baldwin's.
我听说过那地方
Oh   I've heard of that place.
那不是帕萨迪纳最受欢迎的爱尔兰酒吧么
Isn't that Pasadena's favorite Irish watering hole?
没错
Yes.
你有没有在那里
Did you meet
遇到谈得来的人
anyone interesting there
是不是个滥交的红发调酒师
perhaps a promiscuous   redheaded barmaid?
说实话  我不行了
As a matter of fact... I-I-I-I-I can't   I can't
我做不到
I can't do it.
你当然可以  你做得很好  相当令人信服
Sure you can   you're doing fine   it's very believable.
我很抱歉  拉杰  但事实上
I'm sorry   Raj   but the truth is
昨晚我和普丽娅在一起
I was with Priya last night.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
他还满脑子爱尔兰威士忌和熏蛋
He's still light-headed from all the Irish whiskey
一团浆糊呢
and pickled eggs in his system.
你和普丽娅在一起做什么
What were you doing with Priya?
我确信他们是在性交
I believe they engaged in coitus
但更重要的是
but more importantly
如果莱纳德没有半途而废
if Leonard had not abandoned his story
你觉得那个故事可信么
would you have found it plausible?
你上了我妹妹
You slept with my sister?!
对
Yeah.
你怎么可以这样  我们约定好的
How could you? We had a pact.
不好意思  我认为"你情何以堪  她可是我妹妹"
Excuse me   I think "How could you? She's my sister"
总比小孩子的勾勾手约定重要吧
takes precedence over a five-year-old pinky swear.
请允许我指出
May I point out
要是在平行世界  你的朋友会说
in a parallel universe   your friends are saying
"麦琪·麦凯瑞  这名字听起来真可爱"
"Maggie McGarry-- she sounds lovely."
听着  我承认  我是越线了
Look   I-I admit it   I may have crossed a line here
但是拉杰  得了  你妹妹都成年了
but come on   Raj   your sister is a grown woman
对她来说  我不过是块禁忌的白巧克力罢了
and to her   I'm a forbidden piece of white chocolate.
真是难以置信
I don't believe it.
这是对我信任莫大的背叛
This is a terrible betrayal of my trust.
要是我告诉你  我向她献出真心
No   w-w-would it help if I told you
却被她狠狠践踏  你会好受点么
that I offered her my heart   and she kind of stomped on it?
她践踏得多狠
How hard did she stomp?
相当狠
Very hard.
好吧  好受多了
Okay   I'm good.
那个  拉杰
Well   Raj
我只是想说  我绝不会背叛你
I just want to say that I'd never betray your trust.
不会像莱纳德那样  我尊重你
Unlike Leonard   I respect you.
真的么
Really?
当然
Mm-hmm.
你瞒着拉杰  你把他的iPhone
Was it out of respect that you didn't tell Raj
掉进了便池  这算哪门子尊重
about the time you dropped his iPhone in a urinal?
神马  我还把那玩意贴我脸上呢
Dude   I put that thing on my face!
我觉得对拉杰最有趣的欺骗
I think a more amusing violation of Raj's trust
是霍华德居然让他相信
is when Howard convinced him that foreigners give presents
感恩节外国人要送美国人礼物
to Americans on Thanksgiving.
喂  我也没看到你
Hey   I didn't see you giving back
把他送你的史努比刨冰机还给他啊
your Snoopy snow cone maker.
那都是骗我的吗
That was all a lie?
今年的礼物我都准备好了
This year's gifts are already wrapped.
既然我们谈到背叛朋友的事
And as long as we're talking about betraying our friends
何不说说谢尔顿曾经整个月都
how about the month Sheldon spent grinding up insects
把虫子磨碎再混进莱纳德的食物里
and mixing them into Leonard's food?
不好意思
Well   excuse me.
那又不算背叛
That was not a betrayal.
这只是个实验  用来证明
That was an experiment to determine
什么浓度会使食物尝起来有"蛀虫"感
at what concentration food starts tasting "mothy."
你在我食物里放虫子
You put moths in my food?!
为了科学而献身
For science.
你居然用吃过虫子的嘴吻我妹妹
I can't believe you kissed my sister with moth mouth.
你还用了谢尔顿的牙刷呢
Well   I can't believe you used Sheldon's toothbrush.
你用了我的牙刷
You used my toothbrush?
没用刷毛的部分  不过是用那橡皮垫
Not the brush part   just the little rubber thing
剔了剔我的牙  顺便揉了揉牙床
to pick food from my teeth and massage my gums.
好吧  我想我可以说
Okay   I-I think it's safe to say
我们都做过一些
that we've all done some things
不那么光彩的事
we're not particularly proud of.
但是算了  我们是朋友
But come on   we're friends.
朋友会互相谅解彼此的小错误
Friends overlook each other's minor lapses.
所以  霍华德  我很抱歉背叛了我们的约定
For the record   Howard   I'm sorry that I broke our pact.
多谢
Thank you.
我很抱歉把你的iPhone掉进了便池
And I'm sorry about your phone
还有感恩节的事
and Thanksgiving.
既然说到这个
And while we're at it
其实国庆节你也不用替我们洗衣服
you don't have to wash our clothes on the Fourth of July.
既然你们都道歉了
As long as we're apologizing
谢尔顿  很抱歉我用了你的牙刷
Sheldon   I'm   I'm sorry I used your toothbrush.
我也很抱歉...
And I'm sorry...
那这种行为让人忍无可忍
but that behavior is beyond the pale
不可原谅
and cannot be tolerated.
我们不再是朋友了
We are no longer friends.
感恩节我送你个托马斯蒸汽火车头
I got you a talking Thomas the Tank Engine for Thanksgiving.
会喷真的烟吗
With real puffing smoke?
会
Yes.
好吧
All right.
但我记住你了
But I'm watching you.
哎呀  你把史努比拿出来了
Hey   you've got Snoopy out.
我能来一杯刨冰么
Can I have a snow cone?
当然
Well   sure.
味道不错
This is pretty good.
这是什么味道
What flavor is this?
猜猜
Guess.
-木瓜吗  -不是
- Papaya? - No.
-石榴呢  -接近了
- Guava? - You're so close.
我放弃  是什么
I give up.
芒果毛毛虫
Mango caterpillar.
你这是干什么
What are you doing?!
你说你喜欢的呀
You said you liked it.